Some people
break records when it comes to taking care of themselves. A record like
giving a new car from their savings and
giving a driving license to their mother. We will make your smile last
even after retirement. We will
break records like giving surprises to children of all ages and making records of happiness. We
will break records like listening to old stories of dad in a new house. We will break records like not looking at the phone and making records of
happiness. We will break
records like planning for every tomorrow that comes. Those who
take care of their loved ones will not only keep them safe but
also happy.
ICI Prudential's Life
Long Plans are for them. These
provide life long happiness with security. So that they can do
today, tomorrow and ever. A
record of happiness.